(Sheldon:)Why don't you text him that
and see if he backs down?
(Raj:)No.
(Leonard:)I'm going to assert
my dominance face to face.
(Sheldon:)Face to face?
Are you gonna wait for him to sit down
or you gonna stand on the coffee table?
(Leonard:)Hello, Penny. Hello, Kurt.
(Penny(arriving):)Oh, hey, guys.
You having a good time?
(Sheldon:)Given the reaction to my costume...
(Sheldon:)...this party is a scathing indictment
of the American education system.
What? You're a zebra, right?
(Sheldon:)Yet another child left behind.
(Kurt:)And what are you supposed to be,
an elf?
(Leonard:)No, I'm a hobbit.
(Kurt:)What's the difference?
(Leonard:)A hobbit is a mortal, halfling inhabitant
of Middle-earth...
(Leonard:)...whereas an elf
is an immortal, tall warrior.
(Kurt:)So why the hell
would you wanna be a hobbit?
Because he's neither tall nor immortal,
and none of us could be the Flash.
(Kurt:)Well, whatever. Why don't you go hop off
on a quest? I'm talking to Penny here.
(Leonard:)I think we're all talking to Penny here.
I'm not. No offense.